레이첼하고 오늘밤 데이트한다며?
So you and Rachel tonight, huh?
Yeah, yeah, it's actually our first official date.
그래, 첫 공식적인 데이트인 셈이지
Wow! So tonight may be the night.
그럼 중요한 밤이겠네, 긴장돼?
You're nervous?
아니, 사실 내가 제일 잘하는 부분인걸
Nah, no, this is the part I'm actually good at.
What must it be like not to be crippled by fear and self-loathing.
자기혐오에 겁먹지 않고
여자를 대하는게 어떤거야?
뭐.. 괜찮아!
It's okay.
어쩜 그렇게 자신있을 수 있어?
How can you be so confident?
Well, I, I know exactly what I'm gonna do.
어떻게 해야할지 정확히 알고 있으니까
Really? Like you do have a routine?
정말? 어떤 절차라도 있어?
No,no,no,no,no. See, each woman is different.
아니, 모든 여자는 달라
You have to appreciate their uniqueness.
그들의 독특함을 제대로 감상해야 하지
Really?
진짜?
No, I do six things.
아니, 6단계로 진행해
First, I look deep in her eyes, then...
먼저 그녀의 눈을 깊이 들여다 보기
다음엔 키스를 하지
I kiss her.
그리곤 손으로
부드럽게 허벅지를 쓰다듬어
Next, I take my hand and I softly graze her thigh.
You mean like this?
이렇게?
아니, 그렇게 말고
No. Not like that, no.
No, like this.
이렇게 해야지
아, 이제 알겠다
기분 되게 좋은데
Ha, I see what you mean. That's quite nice.
More foosball? / And beer.
축구 게임 한판?
/ 맥주도!
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
Friends 10x02 The One With Ross's Tan
10x03 The One With Ross's Tan
Transcribed by K. Kim
[ 제 작 ]
코리아닷컴 프렌즈동호회 자막팀
자막팀의 동의 없이
수정/배포는 금합니다
자막에 대한 피드백은
동호회 게시판으로 해주십시요
http://club.korea.com/friends
Hey.
안녕
Hey / Hey.
/ 안녕
Hey sweetie.
안녕, 자기야
와우!
Wow!
Hey, stop staring at my wife's legs.
내 마누라 다리 그만 쳐다봐라
No, no. stop staring at your sister's legs.
아니, 네 여동생 다리 그만 좀 쳐다봐라
I'm sorry. It's just ....
미안, 난 그냥...
어떻게 선탠한거야?
How do you get so tanned?
She went to one of those spray-on tan places.
스프레이로 선탠하는데 갔다왔대
스프레이 뿌린거란 말야?
You got a spray-on tan?
Chandler gets pedicures!
챈들러는 '페디큐어'(주) 칠한대!
Hey, what? You do? Like with the, the toe separators?
뭐? 니가?
그 발가락 가르고 하는 그거?
뭐, 뭐가 어때서?
Why? wha..why?
Still, I can't believe that's sprayed on.
스프레이같지가 않은데
정말 괜찮아 보여
I mean it looks really good.
I wonder if I should get one.
나도 한번 해보고 싶어
Sure. Then you should get a miniskirt so you can really show it off.
그럼 내가 미니스커트 하나 사줄테니까
네 다리 구경 좀 해보자
So do you get colors or just french tips?
페디큐어 할 때 색깔도 입히냐?
아니면 그냥 발톱만 붙이냐?
Here.
여기..
Here's the card.
명함 줄께
Thanks.
여기 어딘지 알겠다
Hey, I know where this place is.
It used to be an x-rated video...
예전엔 여기가 성인 비디오..
florist.
...꽃집 이었어
안녕
Hey.
안녕, 피비
Hey Pheebs/ Hey Phoebe.
Ugh, you won't believe who moved back to town.
누가 다시 이사왔는지 알아?
I know. Amanda.
알아, 아만다!
Ugh.
나한테도 전화 했었어
최악이야!
She called me, too.
She's the worst!
Who's Amanda?
아만다가 누군데?
자기 이사오기 전에 살던 여잔데
She's this girl who used to live in the building before you did,
영국으로 이사가더니
억지로 영국식 억양을 흉내내는 여자야
and then she moved to England,
she picked up this fake British accent.
On the machine, this is her message.
응답기에 메시지를 남겼었는데
"Uh, Monica, darling. It's Amanda calling."
"모니카, 딸링~"
"나 아만다양~"
그걸 영국식 억양이라고 한거야?
Are you trying to do a British accent?
Chandler gets pedicures.
챈들러는 페디큐어 칠한대!
그냥 물어보는건데..
그거 몇번이나 더 할 예정이야?
Just so I know, how many more of those can I expect?
Do you know what Amanda said to me when she got me on the phone?
나한테는 전화로 뭐랬는지 알아?
"Oh, so sorry to catch you on your mobile."
"오, 네 모바일(휴대폰)로 전화해서 미안해"
If you didn't want to get me on my mobile,
내 모바일로 전화하기 싫으면
then don't call me on my mobile.
내 모바일로 전화하지 말았어야지!
I know. She's always bragging about all the famous people she's met.
또 자기가 만난 유명인에 대해
얼마나 허풍을 떨어댄다구
Oh, I know!
맞아, "나 빌리 조엘(주)과 같이 잤어"
"Uh...I slept with Billy Joel."
Alright, who hasn't?
누군 안 해본 줄 아나?
Oh, what are we gonna do? I don't want to see her.
아, 어떡하면 좋아
보기 싫은데...
그냥 무시하자
Oh, let's just cut her out.
What?
뭐?
/ 우리 인생에서 무시해버리는거야
Cut her out of our lives.
Just ignore her calls and dodge her until she gets the point.
전화해도 받지 말고 우리가 자길
싫어하는 걸 알때 까지 계속 피하는 거야
Oh, I guess we can try that but that seems so harsh.
그 방법도 괜찮은데 좀 심한 것 같아
Have you ever done that?
그래본 적 있어?
No, had it done to me though.
아니, 근데 당해본 적은 있어
기분은 좋더라구
Feels good.
Alright, Mr. Geller. Right this way.
겔러씨, 이쪽으로 오세요
So, how dark do you want to be?
자, 얼마나 어둡게 해드릴까요?
We have 1, 2 , or 3.
1,2,3단계가 있습니다
Well, uh, I like how you look. What are you?
당신 얼굴 보기 좋은데요 그정도면 몇 단계죠?
Puerto Rican.
전 푸에르토리코(주)계 인데요
/ 2단계요.. 2단계로 해주세요
Two. I think of two.
You're gonna face the red light.
먼저 빨간 등을 보고 계세요
When the red light goes on, the spraying's about to start.
불이 들어오면 곧 스프레이가 뿌려진다는 신호니까
So close your eyes.
눈을 감으시고 스프레이가 끝나면 5까지 세세요
When the spraying stops, count to five.
Pat yourself down to avoid drip marks and turn around
그리고 뭉치지 않게 잘 두드리시고 뒤돌아서세요
so we can get your back. Got it?
그리고나서 등쪽 해드릴께요. 알았죠?
Spray, count, pat and turn.
스프레이 - 세기 - 두드리기 - 돌아서기
Spray, count, and pat.
스프레이 - 세기 - 두드리기.
Wow! You catch on quick.
와, 빨리 이해하시네요
Well, I have a PhD so...
박사학위가 있거든요
One Mississippi, two Mississippi
1 미시시피(주), 2 미시시피, 3 미시...
Three Mississippi.
잠깐~ 잠깐~!!
Why? Why?
I'm not finished counting!
아직.. 아직 덜 셌는데!
얼굴쪽에만 두번 뿌렸어요
You sprayed my front twice!
안돌아섰어요?
You never turned?
No, I barely even got to three Mississippi.
3 미시시피도 세다 말았어요
Mississippi? I said count to five.
미시시피? 그냥 5까지 세라고 했잖아요
'미시시피'는 빼구요?
Mississippi-lessly?
Well, how , how bad is it?
상태가 얼마나 안좋죠?
Not that bad yet
지금은 괜찮지만 4시간만 지나면 점점 어두워질거에요
but it keeps getting darker for the next 4 hours.
So how dark is it gonna get ?
그럼 얼마나 까매질까요?
Huh. You've got sprayed with two twos and
2단계를 두번 뿌렸으니까...
I'm a four?
4단계라구요?
Yeah, but your back's is zero.
하지만 등쪽은 0단계니까 똑같이 4단계로 뿌려줘야 할거에요
You're gonna want to even that out. / Really?
그래요?
다시 들어가시겠어요?
/ 당연하죠!
You might want to get back in there. / Oh, okay!
Wait, wait a minute.
잠깐만요 뒷쪽벽엔 등이 없어요
There's no light on the back wall.
언제 뿌릴지 어떻게 알아요?
How do I know when it's gonna start?
Hello?
이봐요?
악! 악! 내 눈~!!
Oh, oh, my eyes.
아아악~~!!
The same thing happened again!
똑같이 당했잖아요!
You got two more twos?
2단계 두번 더요?
I'm an eight!
8단계네!
Thanks for dinner.
저녁 잘 먹었어
I thought you paid.
네가 계산한 거 아냐?
Ha! I guess we won't be going back there.
우리 이제 다신 거기 못 가겠군
그럼...
So... / Yeah.
Hey, what do you say? We, uh,
우리 의자로 옮겨서 계속하는게 어때?
move this onto the likes of the couch?
I say cheesy line but it's okay.
유치한 말이긴 하지만.. 좋아
What's the matter?
왜그래?
/ 미안, 왜 그랬는지 모르겠네
I don't know. I'm sorry.
I don't remember why I did that.
Okay.
미안해 대체 뭔일인지 모르겠네 너무 긴장했나봐
I'm sorry. Again,
I don't know, I don't know what happened. I must be nervous.
I don't get it. Chandler loved it.
그러게. 챈들러는 좋아하던데
Oh, okay.
I promise, I promise I won't do it again.
다신 안그럴께, 약속해
I really do. I promise. This is gonna be great!
이번엔 멋지게 할거야
OKay. / Okay.
Uh, was that good for you?
참 멋졌지?
No, no, don't get it!
안돼, 받지마
Let the machine pick up.
응답기가 받게 놔둬
/ 아, 그래 또 레이첼이 애 봐달라고
하는건지도 모르니까
Oh, yeah, it could be Rachel asking if someone could babysit again.
It could be Amanda.
아만다일지 모른단 말이야
Oh, you're right! Oh!
아, 맞아!
I was just kidding about Rachel.
레이첼 얘기는 그냥 농담이야
Babysitting's a gas!
애기보는 얘기도 그냥 생각해낸거구
Hello, Monica.
안녕, 모니카? 나, 아만다야
It's Amanda calling again.
I'm in the neighborhood hoping I could pop by your flat.
근처에 온김에
너희 아파트에나 들를까 해서
You're from Yonkers! Your last name is Bouvamanteezy!
넌 '용커스'(주) 출신이야!
성은 또 '부버 만티지'였잖아!
우리 만나자. 메시지 들으면
바로 내 모바일로 전화해줘
Let's see. Should you get this directly,
ring me back on my mobile.
Ok, don't hold thy breath.
코맹맹이 소리좀 내지마
여보세요? 누구 통화중인가요?
Hello, is someone on the line?
Yes, I, I was looking for Monica.
네, 모니카하고 통화하려고 했는데요
Hang on. She's right here.
기다려요 바로 옆에 있어요
자기 전화왔어
Someone's on the phone for you.
We weren't picking up. It's Amanda.
나도 듣고 있었어. 아만다란 말이야
I get pedicures.
나 페디큐어 해요
Hi, Amanda.
안녕, 아만다
Uh, actually, now is, is not a good time.
사실 지금은 좀 곤란해
Dinner tomorrow night?
내일 저녁 먹자고?
그래, 피비하고 같이 나갈께
Okay, Phoebe and I will see you then.
Why? Why? Why didn't you just say no?
왜! 그냥 안된다고 하지!
Well, I said no to her coming over now.
지금 온다는걸 안된다고 했는데
I couldn't say no twice.
안된다는 말을 어떻게 또 해
I've got this uncontrollable need to please people.
원래 난 사람들 즐겁게 못해주면 못견디잖아
Fine! Fine!
잘했군 잘했어
You will not hold up well under torture.
넌 고문같은건 절대 못견딜거야
And you would? / I did.
그러는 넌?
/ 난 견뎠어
Rachel, are you sure you want to do this?
레이첼, 정말 이러는 거 괜찮은 거야?
Absolutely. Absolutely I...
그럼, 당연하지
그냥 너하고 나 사이니까 좀 이상한 것 뿐이야
It's just a little weird. It's you and it's me.
It's just gonna take some getting used to.
적응하기까지 좀 걸릴 뿐이야
Okay. okay well, how can we make it easier?
어떡하면 좀 나을 것 같아?
좋아, 위에서부터 아래로 내려가자
Okay, let's work from the top down.
?
??
???
Just work the bra, Joe!
브라부터 벗기라구, 조이!
/ 알았어
Okay. Got it, yeah.
Okay / Okay
This things is welded shut. / Okay.
단단히 채웠는데?
Alright, turn around. I got to get a look at this thing.
뒤돌아봐, 보면서 하게
Uh , okay.
아얏!
/ 미안!
Ow! / Sorry.
Well, this is romantic.
참 낭만적이네
I'm sorry. This has never happened to me before.
미안해, 이런 일은 없었는데
난 브라 벗기는데는 전문가야.
한손으로도 할 수 있었어
I'm an expert at taking off bras.
I can do it with one hand.
I could do it with my eyes closed.
눈만 깜빡거리고 벗긴 적도 있어
한번은 눈감고 있다가 쳐다봤는데
One time I just looked at one, and it popped open!
저절로 벗겨졌었어
네 브라가 잘못된거야
I blame your bra.
It's a standard issue bra clasp!
이건 그냥 평범한 브라야
Well, then I blame you! Yeah!
그럼 네 탓이야
That's right. You threw me off with all your slapping!
손으로 때리고 밀쳐내서 그래
Ok, look.
Well, I'm really, I'm sorry about that, Joey but
그건 정말 미안하게 생각해
근데 마음속 어디에선가 내 브라를
벗기고 싶어하지 않는건 아닐까?
do you think it may be on, on some level,
you , you don't want to take off my bra?
Nah, I don't have another level!
난 그런 깊은 생각같은거 없어!
Hold on.
잠깐, 뭔가 달라졌는데
There's something different.
네 부인이 추천해준 곳에 가지 말았어야 했는데
I went to that tanning place your wife suggested.
Was that place ' the Sun'?
추천해준 곳이 '태양'이라는 데 였어?
Oh, and it gets worse.
오, 더 심한거 보여줄까?
굉장한데! 너 혼자서
'흑과 백(Ebony & Ivory)'(주)을 듀엣으로 부를 수도 있겠다
Oh my God! You can do a duet of 'Ebony and Ivory' all by yourself.
How could you mess this up?
어쩜 그렇게 될 수가 있어?
It's so easy.
정말 쉽잖아
You go into the booth. You count to five.
부스 안으로 들어가서 다섯을 세고
뒤돌아서면 되잖아
And you turn around!
How do you count to five?
넌 어떻게 다섯을 세는데?
One, two, three... / Damn it!
1, 2, 3, ...
젠장!
Wow! / I know!
나도 알아!
What is up with Miss Hawaiian tropic?
어쩌다 쟤는 미스 하와이(주)가 된거야?
How was your date with Joey?
조이하고 데이트는 어땠어?
Well, it was good,
뭐, 집에 돌아오기까지는 괜찮았어
until we got back to our apartment.
And then we were fooling around and he started to put his hand on my leg...
그리고 같이 분위기 잡고 있다가 조이가 손으로 허벅지를 만지길레
and I kept slapping him away!
손으로 때려버렸어
You didn't like that?
넌 그게 안좋았어?
It wasn't just me. Alright? He freaked out too.
나만 이상했던게 아니라 조이도 이상하더라구
He couldn't even undo my bra.
브라도 못벗기던걸
Wow, really?
와, 정말?
One time he just looked at my bra and it popped open.
한번은 조이가 쳐다보기만 했는데도
내 브라가 벗겨졌었는데
I do not know what's wrong with us.
뭐가 문제인지 모르겠어
I mean, we, we've kissed before and that's been great!
예전에 키스할 때는 굉장히 좋았었어
But this time it was leading somewhere
이번엔 뭔가 어색해서
and I was very aware of the fact that it was Joey touching me.
날 만지고 있는 게 '조이'라는 게
너무 의식이 되더라구
Well, you guys've been friends forever.
너희 둘은 언제나 친구였잖아
Remember the first time that you kissed Ross ? How weird that was?
처음 로스와 키스하고 나서 어땠는지 기억나?
You couldn't stop laughing. You got through that.
웃음이 나와 멈추질 못했었잖아.
잘 넘어 갔잖아
Um hmm. Okay.
그래, 맞아
That's true.
That's true. We can do this.
우린 할 수 있어
You're right. You're right. We can do this.
We're just gonna power through!
헤쳐나갈 수 있어
Hey, uh, Chandler. Can I talk to you for a second?
안녕, 챈들러. 잠깐 이야기좀 할 수 있어?
No need! Problem solved! We are powering through!
그럴 필요 없어! 문제 해결됐으니까
우린 할 수 있어!
Chandler, stop! It's not going to pop open!
챈들러, 그만봐. 그런다고 안벗겨져
You don't know!
네가 어떻게 알아?!
안녕, 피비
/ 안녕
Hi, Phoebe. / Hey
Is Amanda here yet? / No.
아만다 아직 안왔지?
그래
Oh, good. Here, look. I'm so sorry for screwing up that cutting her out plan.
아만다 무시하기로 했던 계획
망쳐놔서 미안해
But I have a new plan.
하지만 새로운 계획이 있어
Chandler agreed to call here in a few minutes with an emergency.
챈들러가 몇 분 후에 위급하게
전화해주기로 했어
Oh, well, okay. What kind of emergency gets us both out of here?
어떤 위급한 상황으로 벗어날건데?
Well, what do you think of Mike and Chandler being in a car accident?
챈들러하고 마이크가 자동차 사고를
당했다고 하면 어떨까?
You're kidding? I love it!
농담해? 딱 좋아!
Hi / Hi
하이~!
/ 하이!
Hello / Hi
It's so nice to see you.
다시 만나서 반가워
Both of you. Look at me!
둘다 나좀 봐봐
Look how young I look!
젊어지지 않았니?
Oh, gosh! We have so much to catch up on.
오, 이런 밀린 이야기가 많네
But first thing's first. Touch my abs.
그래도 이것부터 말해야겠어
내 배좀 만져봐!
I don't exercise at all.
나 운동도 전혀 안한단다
Oh, God. So Monica, you're married.
오, 모니카, 결혼했다며!
Yeah! Yeah! His name is Chandler ...
그래, 남편 이름은 챈들러야
Oh, smell my neck.
오, 내 목 냄새 좀 맡아봐
향수가 아니야
It's not perfume. It's me!
내 자신이지
It's my natural scent.
내 체취야
Musty!
곰팡내 난다
Oh, Gosh. This is brilliant.
정말 멋지지 않니
다시 예전으로 돌아간 것 같아
Gosh, it's just like old times.
I'm so happy you two are friends again.
너희 둘이 다시 친구가 됐다니 기뻐
When were we not friends?
언젠 우리가 친구 아니었나?
Well, it was 1992, and I remember
그러니까 1992년이었지
내가 '이블 크니블'(주)과 잤던 해로 기억하니까
because that was the year I had sex with Evil Knivel.
We were friends in 1992.
1992년에도 우린 친구였는데
I distinctly remember you were dodging her calls,
내가 분명히 기억하는데 피비 네가
모니카전화도 피하고 만나기도 꺼렸지
and trying to avoid seeing her.
You were going to cut me out?
나랑 안 볼려고 했었다고?!
Well, kind of. / Oh my God!
뭐, 조금...
/ 맙소사!
Oh bugger! Should I not have said that?
이런, 바보같이..
말하면 안되는거였어?
Ugh! I feel like a perfect arse.
완전히 '똥구녕(arse)'(주) 됐네
In America, you're just an ass!
미국에선 넌 '똥구멍(ass)'이 된거야
Hello.
여보세요?
Chandler, what's wrong?
챈들러, 무슨 일이야?
Oh my God! Are you alright?
어머, 안다쳤어?
Yeah. I'll be right there.
그래, 금방 갈께
I..I'm so sorry but Chandler was in a car accident.
미안하지만 챈들러가 자동차 사고가 났다고 해서
Oh, oh my God! / Yeah!
이런, 마이크도 같이 있었대?
Was Mike with him? / Nope!
아니!
Hey / Hey
Got Champagne? / Yes, ma'am. Ready to power through!
샴페인은?
네, 마님!
뚫고나갈 준비 됐습니다!
Excellent, okay. Stick it in the ice bucket.
좋았어! 얼음통에 넣고
수화기는 들어놓았으니
The phone is off the hook.
And in the interest of powering through. / Woo!
뚫고 나갈 일만 남았군
Okay, sexy, sexy.
자, 쎅시, 쎅시...
Very sexy. sexy.
진짜 쎅시하게...
Alright, let's do it!
자, 이제 시작하자!
Okay, you're scaring me a little bit.
잠깐, 좀 무섭게 구는거같아
Oh, get over it, solider. We got to do this! / Okay.
이겨내야 해, 병사!
우린 해내야만 한다고!
그래
Okay, ha ha. You like that, huh?
자, 하... 하고싶다 이거지?
Oh, yeah. / You like that?
하고 싶다고?
분위기 좀 달궈 볼까?
Let's kick this into high gear, huh?
Yeah, baby, I'll show you how we do it.
예, 베이비~ 이제 놀아 볼까?
/ 자,자,잠깐만!
No, no, no, You kneed me in my masters! / What?
무릎으로 거시길 누르고 있잖아
뭐? 이런...
Oh my God! I'm so sorry.
정말 미안해
조이, 괜찮아?
Joey, are you okay?
Soldier down!
병사가 전사한거 같아~!
We are not friends with Phoebe any more.
피비는 이제 우리 친구 아냐
If she asks I protested a little but okay.
피비가 원한다면 좀 반항은 하겠지만...
그래!
Oh, Chandler. Thank God you're alive.
챈들러, 살아있다니 정말 다행이다
모니카, 밖에서 잠깐 이야기좀 할래?
Monica, can I talk to you outside for a minute?
너한테 할 말.. 없어
I have nothing...to say to you.
Wow, my flat is twice this size.
와, 내 아파트가 이거 두배는 되겠다
Please Monica, in the hall.
모니카, 복도에서 좀 볼래?
오, 끔찍한 사고였나봐요!
Ooh, that accident must have been terrible!
You look positively ghastly!
굉장히 핼쓱해 보여요
Well, aren't you a treat?
그럼, 치료좀 해줘봐요
I can't believe you tried to cut me out.
날 안보려고 했었다는게 안믿겨져
Why, Phoebe? Why?
피비, 왜 그랬는데?
It was, it was right after we were living together
너랑 같이 살게 되면서부터
and you were driving me crazy, okay?
너때문에 미칠 지경이었다구, 알아?
You were really controlling and compulsive and shrill!
넌 정말 주도면밀하고 강박적인데다가
목소리도 높았어
지금하고 똑같잖아!
I'm still all those things!
You're also so generous, and kind and scrappy.
지금의 넌 다정하고 친절하기도 하고
또 정리도 잘해
I am scrappy.
나 정리 잘해
Exactly. Look, no matter what I tried to do, I couldn't keep you out of my life!
정말이야, 내가 무슨 짓을 하더라도
널 내 삶에서 쫓아낼 수가 없었거든
Of all the people I've cut out,
내가 관계를 끝낸 사람들 중에서
you were the only one who ever clawed her way back in.
너만 유일하게 자기 자리로 기어들어왔어
내가 정리를 잘 해서?
It must be because I'm scrappy.
그래, 그리고 난 네가 제자리로
되돌아와줘서 기뻐
Yeah, you are. And I'm so glad that you fought your way back in.
난 너없이는 아무것도 할 줄 모르니까
Because I don't know what I would do without you.
I don't know what I would do without you. / Oh.
나도 너없이는 아무것도 할 수 없어
자, 이제 들어가봐야겠다
Now I guess we should get back in.
I mean you gave me another chance
너도 나한테 기회를 줬으니
우리도 아만다에게 같은 기회를 줘야지
I guess we should do the same for Amanda.
그래, 맞아
Yeah I guess, you're right.
Can you believe it? I've never had any professional dance training.
댄스 강습 받아본 적도 없는데
이정도니 놀랍지 않아요?
자, 어떻게 하시는지 말씀드릴께요
Now let me explain how this works.
You go into the booth and you ...
부스 안으로 들어가셔서...
/ 그만 설명하시죠, 글렌다양
I'm gonna stop you right there, Glenda.
Does it look like this is my first time? Ah?
제가 초보자로 보이세요? 네?
Now I want four 2's and
2단계로 네번 뿌려주시구요
I want them all on my back.
꼭 등쪽에 뿌려주세요
Okay.
알았어요
Wait a minute, there's two sets of nozzles. Which one is it?
잠깐만요, 꼭지가 양쪽에 있잖아요!
어느쪽에서 나오는거죠?
Which, which, which, which one is it?
어느, 어느 쪽에서 나오냐구요!
Oh, son of a bitch!
이런, 빌어먹을!
우리 문제가 뭘까?
What is the matter with us?
Oh, I know what's the matter with me.
내 문제가 뭔지는 알겠는데
No, I mean with us.
내말은... 우리 사이 말이야
You know? I mean it's just supposed to be this...
어쩌면 이게 당연한지도 몰라
이렇게까지...
difficult?
어려운게
I don't know.
나도 모르겠어
That fake British woman's a real bitch but she sure can dance.
저 짝퉁 영국여자, 나쁜여자긴 한데
춤은 제대로 추더라
Hey /Hi
Hey, listen. Can I ask you a question?
잠깐, 뭐 좀 물어봐도 돼?
When you and Monica first hooked up, was it weird going from
모니카랑 사귀기 시작했을 때
친구사이에서 그 이상으로 발전한다는게
friends to more than that?
이상하진 않았어?
Kinda, you know, sneaking around having to hide from you guys.
조금은... 너희들 피해서 숨어다니는게...
아니, 내말은...
No, no, no, no, I mean...
성적으로 말이야
Sexually.
Yeah, I...Was there a part of you that, that felt like it was ....
그래, 뭔가 정말 잘못하고
있다는 느낌은 없었어?
really wrong?
아니, 없었어
옳다고 느꼈는걸
Actually no.
No, it felt right.
You know? It felt like, uh,
I can't believe we haven't been doing this the whole time.
그 이전까지 해보지 않았다는게 믿기지 않을 정도로
I can tell from your expressions that's the good news you were hoping for.
반응을 보아하니 너희가 기대하던
좋은 소식이었던 것 같군
자, 그럼 계속해서
기쁜 소식을 전하러 가볼까?
Well, I'm gonna go continue to spread the joy.
Well, just becuase that happened that way for them doesn't mean it has to happen that way for us.
쟤네 둘이 그랬다고 해서
꼭 우리들도 그러라는 법은 없잖아?
Yeah, yeah. Absolutely.
그래, 당연하지
I mean, just because something's difficult doesn't mean that you quit.
뭔가가 어렵다고 해서
항상 그만두는건 아니잖아
Right, totally. / Yeah.
그래, 맞아
/ 그래
그러니까 우린 될 때까지
So we just keep trying and trying until we do it.
계속.. 노력해보는거야
Yeah, and if it doesn't work,
그래, 그렇게 해도 안되면
우린 섹스하지 않는 커플로 살면 되지
-then we'll just be one of those couples that never have sex! -That's a plan!
그래도 되겠네
I did not see this coming.
이렇게 될줄은 몰랐어
I know.
그래
I don't get it. I mean..
이게 내가 원하는거라고 확신했는데
I was so sure this is what I wanted.
Me too.
나도
모니카하고 챈들러는
어떻게 해낼 수 있었을까?
How come Monica and Chandler could do it?
I guess they weren't as good friends as we are.
아마 우리 사이처럼
좋은 친구 사이는 아니었나보지
어...
Oh....
네말이 맞는거같아
I bet you're right.
So...
그럼...
Yeah.
그래
I love you.
사랑해
I love you, too.
나도 사랑해
-Alright, I'm going to bed. -Yeah, me too.
이제 그만 자야겠다
그래, 나도
Oh, yeah. I'm not going anywhere for a while.
우, 좀만 더 있다 가야겠다
[번 역]
신우철 (berlitz@korea.com)
[싱 크]
변정주 (jungjoo@kaist.ac.kr)
[테스트]
이상민 (albireon@korea.com)
친구야, 나야, 챈들러
문좀 열어줘
Dude, it's Chandler, let me in.
Go away!
저리 가!
아무도 안볼래
I don't want to see anybody.
I know. I went to the tanning placen and the same thing happened to me.
알아, 나도 선탠하러 갔다가
똑같이 당했다니까
그러니까 문좀 열어봐
/ 정말?
You have to let me in. / Really?
Did you count Mississippi-ly?
'미시시피' 붙여서 셌어?
You, you're not tanned.
선탠 안했잖아?
No. I just had to get a picture of this.
안했지
사진 한장 찍어두고 싶어서
다음에 보자!
I'll see you later.